tractorbynet.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy - TractorByNet

## TractorByNet Privacy Basics

**What personal information does TractorByNet store on its servers?**

We store your IP address for all website visitors, as well as the e-mail address and “location” as entered by the user only when they create a user account. If you have placed an order from our store, we also store your address(es) and phone number(s) as well.

**Does TractorByNet share or sell personal data of its users to third parties?**

We do not, with the exception of quote request forms and contact forms that our users complete. In those cases, personal data is shared with the third parties that receive the data from those forms (data entered on the form). This includes:

  * Private messages sent from user-to-user that include personal data in the message body
  * Contact forms on classified ads
  * Quote request forms

In each case, the data you enter on the on-site forms will be shared with the third parties relevant to the communication or quote request.

**What information do the ads on TractorByNet gather and store?**

We display ads from a number of third party networks as well as our own in-house advertising network, which includes ad delivery technology controlled by TractorByNet. The only personal data that those third parties collect is your IP address and cookie information. That information is used to display ads to you on other websites you visit. You can opt out of our retargeting ads by visiting the following links:

Please check the “partner privacy policies” section below for more information and links to third party ad delivery and partner privacy policies.

**Does TractorByNet use cookies? Do the cookies store personal data?**

Yes. The anonymous cookie assigned by TractorByNet tracks your username and password.

Our ad networks may also assign anonymous cookies to each user. These cookies serve two primary purposes:

  * Track how many times an ad is served to a particular user and we stop serving the ad after a certain number of views.
  * Limit the number of times we serve ads to each user’s browser.

* * *

## Personal Data Download & Deletion

**Q: How can a user download all personal information stored on TractorByNet’s servers?**

A: Forum members can visit [this link](http://www.tractorbynet.com/forums/profile.php?do=editprofile) to view the personal information we have stored. This only applies to registered members. Store customers can view the personal information we have stored at [this link](http://store.tractorbynet.com/login.asp).

**Q: How can a user delete all personal data stored by TractorByNet?**

A: Deleting all personal data requires that we delete your e-mail address from your user account. Please e-mail contact@tractorbynet.com with your request with the subject line “delete personal data” and we will remove your personal data not more than 30 days after your request is received.

* * *

## Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering, submitting a quote request, or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously and not submit any information.

Google, PointRoll, Tribal Fusion, and other companies, as third party vendors, use cookies to serve ads on TractorByNet.com. Use of these tracking cookies enable our vendors to serve ads to users based on their visit to TractorByNet.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

To process transactions

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

To send periodic emails such as newsletters, promotions from TractorByNet.com, and site updates.

To fulfill quote requests.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, servicing you, or providing price quotes on sales or services in conjunction with user requested quote requests, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Partner Privacy Policies**

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.com.

**Terms of Use**

Please also visit our Terms of Use section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.tractorbynet.com/content/terms-of-use/>

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [online privacy policy](http://www.tractorbynet.com/content/privacy-policy).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 10/24/2018

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

TractorByNet.com  
P.O. Box 845  
Carlsbad, California 92018  
USA
